[Music]
businesses often sell different product
through the different sales channels
ability to activate specific sales
channels simplifies workflow and gives
you full control on which products will
be sold through which channel let's see
it in the demo you can set up multiple
sales channels in the Shopify
admin on the Shopify sales channels page
you can activate any available channels
as
needed navigate to products and Export
them as Shopify
products then explore the created
product in Shopify and check the sales
channels to ensure it matches the
settings on the Shopify sales channels
page if if you haven't configured the
Shopify sales channels page your
products will default to the online
store thank you for watching you can
find details about this capability in
the release node also check other videos
on Shopify connector enhancements you
can find links in the in the description